https://www.hoytmeter.com/privacy-policy

All Categories
Analog Panel Meters
2000 Series2100 Series2700 Series3100 Series4000 Series5000 Series6000 Series250 DegreeDIN MetersSwitchboard MetersHST SeriesIndustrial MetersMoving Magnet MetersEdgewise MetersVU MetersMeter MovementsAutomotive TestAccessories
Digital Panel Meters
3.0 LED3.5 LED3.5 LCD4.5 LCD3.5 LCD Loop Powered 4.5 LCD Loop Powered 3.5 LCD Voltage Powered 4.5 LCD Voltage PoweredAccessories
Synchroscopes
Digital MultiFunction Meters
Advanced Panel MetersDigital AmmetersDigital VoltmetersFrequency MetersBargraphsDigital Power & Energy MetersProcess Meters
Test & Measurement
Cable Tracers & TestersClamp MetersELCB TestersEarth Resistance TestersHigh VoltageInsulation TestersInsulation & MF TestersAudio & SoundLoop TestersMultimetersNetwork AnalyzersMilliohm & Ohm MetersSafety Voltage DetectorsVoltage/Continuity TestersPhase TestersRCBLow Voltage DetectorsElectrical Test LeadsAnalog Leakage MetersAC Voltage Proving UnitsPower MetersVarious Instruments
Power
Current TransformersVoltage TransformersShuntsToroids
Electromechanical
RelaysDisconnect SwitchesTransducersTransmitter
Hour & Elapsed Time Meters
PRODUCTS
BRANDS
AFFILIATES
$0.00
You have no items in your shopping cart.
Home
/
Hoyt Meter Privacy Policy
Privacy Policy
Hoyt Electrical Instrument Works, Inc. is committed to protecting any personal information that you may provide to us. Further, Hoyt Electrical Instrument Works, Inc. recognizes the importance of informing you how we treat information about you that we may receive from this Site.
Information Collected In general, you can visit this Site without telling us who you are or revealing any information about yourself. Our web servers may collect the domain names, but not the e-mail addresses, of visitors. In addition, there are portions of this Site where we may need to collect personal information from you for a specific purpose, such as to provide you with certain information you request. The information collected from you may include your name, address, telephone, fax number, or e-mail address. You may refuse any request for personal information, unless required at time of checkout. This Site is not intended for persons under 13 years of age. We do not knowingly solicit or collect personal information from or about children, and we do not knowingly market our products or services to children.
Use of Collected Information Domain name information that we collect is not used to personally identify you. It is used to measure viewer statistics, such as the number of viewers that visit the Site, pages viewed, etc. We use this information to measure the use of our Site and to improve the content of our Site.
E-mail addresses collected through the Site may be used for marketing or promotional purposes, and you may opt-out at any time.
When other information is collected from you, such as your name and e-mail address, Hoyt Electrical Instrument Works, Inc. will make reasonable efforts to let you know at the time of collection how this information will be used. Usually, the personal information you provide will only be used to respond to an inquiry you make or to process your request. This information may be shared with support partners, but only if necessary to fulfill your request or for related purposes. Hoyt Electrical Instrument Works, Inc. does not share, sell, or lease personal information about you to any third-parties for their marketing use. Hoyt Electrical Instrument Works, Inc. will release information about you if you direct it to do so, if Hoyt Electrical Instrument Works, Inc. is required by law to do so, or in other legally limited circumstances.
Links to Other Sites The Hoyt Electrical Instrument Works, Inc. website may contain links to other sites such as authorized distributors and sales affiliates. While Hoyt Electrical Instrument Works, Inc. makes reasonable efforts to try to link only to sites that share our high standards and respect for privacy, Hoyt Electrical Instrument Works, Inc. is not responsible for the content, security, or privacy practices employed by other sites.
Security of Collected Information Hoyt Electrical Instrument Works, Inc. maintains strict physical, electronic, and administrative safeguards to protect your personal information from unauthorized or inappropriate access. Hoyt Electrical Instrument Works, Inc. restricts access to information about you to those Hoyt Electrical Instrument Works, Inc. workers who need to know the information to respond to your inquiry or request. Workers who misuse personal information are subject to disciplinary action.
Access to Collected Information You may review and update the information that you provide to Hoyt Electrical Instrument Works, Inc. through this Site by contacting us as described below or by signing into your account.
Contacting Us If you have any questions about this privacy policy, please use the Contact Us page. Hoyt Electrical Instrument Works, Inc. welcomes your questions and suggestions about this privacy policy.
Changes to this Policy Please check this privacy policy periodically to inform yourself of any changes. Although Hoyt Electrical Instrument Works, Inc. reserves the right to modify or supplement this privacy policy, Hoyt Electrical Instrument Works, Inc. will provide notice to you on this Site of any major changes for at least 30 days following the change.
Categories
Analog Panel Meters
2000 Series
2100 Series
2700 Series
3100 Series
4000 Series
5000 Series
Latest products
ST-375 Rotary S..
$182.99
APM AC CT Meter
$72.00
7016 IN Digital..
$2,844.99
See All
Special Products
4NO4 Current Trans..
$141.00
$99.95
Add to Cart
See All
This website requires cookies to provide all of its features. For more information on what data is contained in the cookies, please see our Privacy Policy Page. To accept cookies from this site, please click the Allow button.
Allow
